Amiri Baraka papers 6909686
Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Series VIII: Audio/Visual, 1959-2007
  - Audio, 1973-2007
    - Audiocassettes, 1959-2003
      - Charlie Parker-Classic Bird, 1996; 1 audiocassettes (Box 86)
      - Combomatic: "We Called it Hep Hop", 1968; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026818388
      - Connections Tyrone Jefferson, 1994; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
      - Coping with Death: A Personal Story, November 14, 1997
        "As part of the series, The End of Life: Exploring Death in America, NPR's Vertamae Grosvenor tells how she and her eight-year-old grandson, Oscar, tried to come to terms with the loss of his father in a car crash."--NPR
      - Crazy Jane Poems, undated; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026818248
      - Deliverance B. Smith, 1991; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026819724
      - Dick Gregory 21st Century, undated; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
      - Dr. Robert Young on WLIB w/Gary Byrd, 1966; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026819945
      - Drama: Panel 4, 1986; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026818760
      - Ed Dorn "Satirical Verses", 2000; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026818329
      - End of Life: Death and Dying; PEN/Faulkner reading, 1997; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026819767
      - Ernie Watts: Unity, undated; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
      - Excerpt Newark 1953, 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026819805
      - Grenada: The Fall of the Revolution, undated; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026819759
      - Holy Bible: Red Leter Edition, 1998; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026819589
      - Hugh: Ragin, undated; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026818183
      - Interview, undated; 1 audiocassettes (Box 82D)
        26818060
      - Jazz Study Group: Jazz and Africa, 1997-03-06; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026818833
      - Jazzspeak: A Word Collection, undated; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
      - Jeffrey Mumford: Improvisations, undated; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026819708
      - Jerome and Carl Thomas, undated; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026819848
      - Jerome Washington, 1991-05-24; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026819490
      - Jesse Jackson, undated; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026818736
      - Joe Henderson Inner Urge, undated; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
      - John Blake, undated; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026818795
      - John Kirby's Band, undated; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026819651
      - Juba's Poetry, 2000-11-13; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026818370
      - Judy Bady, undated; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026819635
      - Kenneth Tyler, undated; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026819457
      - Kikora Round Midnight, undated; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026819899
      - Labor of Love: The Life of Sarah Vaughan NJPAC, 1999-03-27; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026818175
      - Lad Johnson, 1989; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026819791
      - Larry Woods Alone, 1991; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026819554
      - Lectures: Traditions of Revolution, symposium, 1994; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026818752
      - Leo Johnson, undated; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026818256
      - Leo Johnson Quartet, 1988-04-16; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026818345
      - Leo Johnson Trio, 0988-01-09; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026818396
      - Leo Johnson, 1988-02-20; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026818310
      - Leroi Jones, undated; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026818728
      - Life and [illegible] of Bumpy Johnson, 1986-09-03; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026818230
      - Live SoulSpeak, undated; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026818078
      - Live SoulSpeak, June 1999; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026818086
      - Live Therapeutic Soulspeak Session, 1999; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026818116
      - Los Navegantes, 1988-01-30; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026818205
      - Lynn Hope: Don't Worry About Me, undated; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026819546
      - Malcolm X and the Black Liberation Movement, undated; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026818094
      - Manifestation Axiom Collection II, 1993; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
      - Many Voices of Soulspeak, undated; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026819686
      - Michael Pintard: Multiple Comings; radio segment from the 1990 New Orleans Jazz and Heritage Festival, 1991; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026819503
      - Miles, Dizzy by Amiri Baraka, undated; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026818744
      - Milladoiro, undated; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026819880
      - Modlibo's Wake, 2003-11-24; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026819740
      - Mother Afrika, and Afrikans, Will Be Free, 1998; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026819520
      - Moving Hearts-The Story, undated; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026819813
      - Mozamgola Caper, 1986; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026819864
      - Music for Oboe and Orchestra, undated; 1 audiocassettes (Box 86)
      - N.O. LA Jazz Heritage Festival, undated; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026818124
      - Nasar Abadey and Supernova, 1983; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026819538
      - NY Art Quarte, 1999-06-13; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026818213
      - Our Ancestral Food, 1994; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026819414
      - Panic * DJ!, 1988; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026819953
      - Paul Mandelbaum First Words: Earliest Writing from Favorite Contemporary Authors, 1995; 1 audiocassettes (Box 86)
      - PEN/Faulkner Award for Fiction, 1989; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026819929
      - Pinkie Gordon Lane / New Letters, 1991-02-18; 1 audiocassettes (Box 82D)
      - Playthell Benjamin on WLIB, 1992-08-20; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026818787
      - Playwright aka Leroi Jones - Amiri Baraka - The Real Legacy of Malcolm X vs. Spike Lee's Film "X", 1993; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026819996
      - Professor Louie, undated; 1 audiocassettes (Box 86)
      - Pura Fe & Soni: Ladies Choice, undated; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026819627
      - Robert Silverman Jazz, undated; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026819562
      - Roy Campbell New Kingdom, 1992; 1 audiocassettes (Box 86)
      - Sandang & Waakaw, 2000; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
      - Sax Storm and Grand Central, undated; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
      - Self Test, undated; 1 audiocassettes (Box 82D)
      - Shannon Gibbons: There's Only You, undated; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
      - Side I - Early Years, undated; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026818159
      - Soul Speak Speakings Pre-Release, undated; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026818140
      - Stewart Cunningham and the Sports Jazz Ensemble, 1998; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
      - The Community Jazz Quintet, undated; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026819775
      - The Coupe, undated; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026818418
      - The Dynamics, undated; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026819783
      - The Roots, undated; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026818353
      - The Shaman and the Nigga God, 1997; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026819872
      - Ti Raoul / Ti Emile, 1982-04-03; 1 audiocassettes (Box 82D)
      - Toure Kunda-Amadou Tilo, 1984; 1 audiocassettes (Box 86)
      - Tribal Voice AKA Grafitti Man, undated; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026819660
      - Tribute to Abbey, undated; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026818337
      - Tribute to Miles, undated; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
      - Umberto Petri: Piano Solos, undated; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026819473
      - University of Massachusetts Sel., undated; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026818299
      - Untitled 1, undated; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026818043
      - Untitled 2, undated; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
      - Vea Williams-You've Got this Space (Now Make it Work for You), 1990; 1 audiocassettes (Box 86)
      - Victor Arenciba Song, 2002; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026819961
      - Vocal Sampling: Una Forma Mas, 1995; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
      - Walking for Peace, undated; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026819511
      - Walter Bland Trio, 1999-07-15; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026819970
      - We Speak, 1994; 1 audiocassettes (Box 82D)
      - Wm.Loren Katz: White Way, undated; 1 audiocassettes (Box 90)
        0026819465
    - CD, 1990-2007
      - Amiri Baraka Lecture on Revolutionary Poetry, 7/6/1994; 2 compact disks (Box 82D)
      - "Trouble Inna Streets,", undated (Box 86)
      - Coldcut, "Sound Mirrors,", 2006 (Box 86)
      - "Inner Spirits: A Selection of Poems by Clinton N. Dozier,", undated (Box 86)
      - The Jack Kerouac Collection, 1990 (Box 86)
      - J. Michael The Demo, undated (Box 86)
      - Steve Dalachinsky, Matthew Shipp Phenomena of Interference, undated (Box 86)
      - Los Dorados-Turbulencia, 2006 (Box 86)
      - John Trudell-Tribal Voice, undated (Box 86)
      - Mumia Abu-Jamal Prison Radio: Dispatches from Death Row, 2007 (Box 86)
      - Seneca James Executive Decisions, 2004 (Box 86)
      - "Hot 97 #44,", undated (Box 86)
      - "My Oldies Disk 2,", undated (Box 86)
      - "Ceasefire Allstars,", undated (Box 86)
      - Ms. Gerri Morrison The Story: That's Jazz!, 2006 (Box 86)
    - DATs, 2000
      - Terry Dexter, EQ'd TV Mixes, 2000; 4 digital audio tapes (Box 82D)
    - Open Reel Audio Tapes, 1961-1974
      - Address at Miami University, May 6, 1974; 1 open reel audiotapes; 7-inch reel (Box 92)
        (0026818540)
      - Amiri Baraka, February 15, 1976; 1 open reel audiotapes; 5-inch reel (Box 93)
        (0026819252)
      - Amiri Baraka Recorded at Northern Illinois University, May 20, 1971; 1 open reel audiotapes; 7-inch reel (Box 92)
        (0026819090)
      - Amiri Baraka and James Baldwin readings, February 4, 1970; 2 open reel audiotapes; 12-inch reel (Box 94)
        (0026819279) and (0026817861)
        Committee for Unified Newark benefit reading with LeRoi Jones (Amiri Baraka) and James Baldwin. Labelled "Amiri Baraka, Lewis Byron" and "Declaration of Independence; Porgy and Bess; Amiri Baraka and James Baldwin, February 4, 1970"
      - Amiri Baraka, WBAI Notes, Wed 10/14, undated; 1 open reel audiotapes; 12-inch reel (Box 94)
        (0026819260)
      - Antonin Artaud, April 1961; 1 open reel audiotapes; 7-inch tape (Box 91)
        (0026817918)
        Radio plays
      - ARTRA, undated; 1 open reel audiotapes; 12-inch reel (Box 94)
        (0026819392)
      - Baraka at Dunbar High School, Chicago, 1968; 1 open reel audiotapes; 7-inch reel (Box 93)
        (0026818914)
      - Black Forum "Last Poets", March 5-6, 1971; 12 open reel audiotapes; 7-inch tape (Box 91)
        (0026819120, 0026817977, 0026819112, 0026819023, 0026818906, 0026819155, 0026817993, 0026819180, 0026819104, 0026817985, 0026817810, 0026818957)
      - Black Newark 3/31, undated; 1 open reel audiotapes; 7-inch reel (Box 92)
        (0026818515)
      - Black Newark and Congress of African Peoples, undated; 2 open reel audiotapes; 7-inch reel (Box 92)
        (0026818892)
      - Black Newark Reel #2, undated; 1 open reel audiotapes; 7-inch reel (Box 92)
        (0026818655)
      - Black Newark: 3rd Week of Union Strike, undated; 1 open reel audiotapes; 7-inch reel (Box 92)
        (0026818930)
      - Black Panther Benefit, May 25, 1967; 1 open reel audiotapes; 7-inch tape (Box 91)
        (0026817900)
      - Byron Pope Ensemble, October 25, 1968; 1 open reel audiotapes; 7-inch tape (Box 91)
        (0026818590)
        Recorded live at the Eagles Auditorium, Seattle. Second set. Personnel: Byron Pope, Alphonse Wynn, Steve Solder, Robert Moody
      - Chairman Amiri Baraka Interview, May 29, 1975; 1 open reel audiotapes; 5-inch reel (Box 93)
        (0026819228)
      - Charlie Corcoran - This is Mine, undated; 1 open reel audiotapes; 7-inch tape (Box 91)
        (0026818604)
        side 1 is Baraka speech; side 2 is radio segment on the Apollo IV mission
      - Colin D. Edwards, undated; 1 open reel audiotapes; 7-inch tape (Box 91)
        (0026818850)
        Side 1: Articulations of Negro Revolt. Side 2: The White Integrationists; Reaction to Selma
      - Concert, Sheila 1st generation, December 21, 1962; 1 open reel audiotapes; 7-inch tape (Box 91)
        (0026817829)
      - Concert: Champion Jack Dupree, undated; 1 open reel audiotapes; 7-inch tape (Box 91)
        (0026818639)
        Intermission: Jack DuPree overture (18:20; Act II: Sketches (4:36); Al's Solo; Ronnie's Solo (3:10); Missa Luba (13:48)
      - Congress of African Peoples: Immersions/impressions, 1970; 1 open reel audiotapes; 12-inch reel (Box 94)
        (0026819988)
      - Congress of Afrikan People. Afrikan Women's Conference, undated; 1 open reel audiotapes; 5-inch reel (Box 93)
        (0026818680)
      - Congress of Afrikan Peoples, October 16, 1970; 1 open reel audiotapes; 12-inch reel (Box 94)
        (0026819325)
      - Congress of Afrikan Peoples 14, Delegates from Africa #2, reel #1, 1970; 1 open reel audiotapes; 12-inch reel (Box 93)
        (0026817870)
      - Congress of Afrikan Peoples 18: Pharoah Sanders, 09/07/70, 1970; 2 open reel audiotapes; 12-inch reel (Box 93)
        (0026819333, 0026819341)
      - Congress of Afrikan Peoples 31, Amiri (Imamu) Baraka #2 part 3, 1970; 1 open reel audiotapes; 12-inch reel (Box 93)
        (0026819295)
      - Congress of Afrikan Peoples 9, #1, Louis Farrakhan etc, 1970; 1 open reel audiotapes; 12-inch reel (Box 93)
        (0026819317)
      - Congress of Afrikan Peoples, 13: Resolutions on Workshops, 1970; 1 open reel audiotapes; 12-inch reel (Box 93)
        (0026819309)
      - Congress of Afrikan Peoples, 15 #3 Julian Bond, 1970; 1 open reel audiotapes; 12-inch reel (Box 93)
        (0026817888)
      - HDS-up, undated; 1 open reel audiotapes; 5-inch reel (Box 93)
        (0026818493)
      - Imamu Baraka Band on Black Music, January 12, 1971; 1 open reel audiotapes; 7-inch reel (Box 92)
        (0026817934)
      - Imamu Reading "Larry Rivers" Poem, undated; 1 open reel audiotapes; 7-inch reel (Box 93)
        (0026819066)
      - Imamu, Julian Bond, Alex Ponsett, Richard Hatcher, undated; 1 open reel audiotapes; 5-inch reel (Box 93)
        (0026819236)
      - Imamu: Need for Community Organizing and Political Empowerment, 1974; 1 open reel audiotapes; 7-inch reel (Box 93)
        (0026818973)
      - Interview, August 13, 1974; 2 open reel audiotapes; 7-inch tape (Box 91)
        (0026819007, 0026818965)
      - Ideas: LeRoi Jones interviewed by Austin Clarke, 1968 January 17; 1 open reel audiotapes; 7-inch tape (Box 91)
        (0026818841)
      - Jass, Black Expression, November 20, 1970; 1 open reel audiotapes; 7-inch reel (Box 92)
        (0026818876)
      - Jesse Jackson Speech at 1970 meeting of Congress of African Peoples, 1 open reel audiotapes; 12-inch reel (Box 94)
        (0026819287)
      - John Coltrane Interview, November 1966; 1 open reel audiotapes; 5-inch reel (Box 93)
        (0026817853)
      - LaMonte Young Concert, August 26, 1962; Young, La Monte; 1 open reel audiotapes; 7-inch tape (Box 91)
        (0026818566)
      - Last Poets, undated; 2 open reel audiotapes; 7-inch tape (Box 91)
        (0026819139, 0026819171)
        JU 2-1070
      - Leroi Jones at Cortland State College, December 04, 1968; 1 open reel audiotapes; 7-inch reel (Box 92)
        (0026817950)
      - LeRoi Jones at Idaho State University, February 25, 1969; 1 open reel audiotapes; 7-inch reel (Box 92)
        (0026819015)
      - Leroi Jones at Loyola University "Cultural Nationalism", March 2, 1969; 1 open reel audiotapes; 7-inch reel (Box 92)
        (0026817896)
      - LeRoi Jones From Say Brother #20, December 05, 1968; 1 open reel audiotapes; 7-inch reel (Box 92)
        (0026818981)
      - Leroi Jones in Los Angeles California, June 9, 1968; 1 open reel audiotapes; 7-inch reel (Box 92)
        (0026818922)
        Side 2: School Tape Recorder
      - Leroi Jones Milwaukee, December 12, 1968; 1 open reel audiotapes; 7-inch reel (Box 92)
        (0026817942)
      - LeRoi Jones Program, dub, November 23, 1970; 1 open reel audiotapes; 7-inch reel (Box 92)
        (0026819040)
      - LeRoi Jones, NYC, tape 1, January 21, 1968; 1 open reel audiotapes; 7-inch reel (Box 92)
        (0026818868)
      - LeRoi Jones, Parkman, December 12, 1968; 1 open reel audiotapes; 7-inch reel (Box 92)
        (0026818949)
      - Leroi Reading, undated; 1 open reel audiotapes; 7-inch reel (Box 92)
        (0026818574)
      - Letter to New York Times, Poem, Interview, undated; 1 open reel audiotapes; 7-inch tape (Box 91)
        (0026819147)
      - Love Eternal Dance, undated; 1 open reel audiotapes; 7-inch tape (Box 91)
        (0026818523)
        Love Eternal Dance / The Heart Doctrine
      - Music and WBAI segment [illegible title], undated; 1 open reel audiotapes; 7-inch reel (Box 93)
        (0026818507)
      - Need for More Daycare Centers in New York; Urban League, undated; 1 open reel audiotapes; 7-inch tape (Box 91)
        (0026819058)
      - New Well, April 30, 1971; 1 open reel audiotapes; 7-inch tape (Box 91)
        (0026818990)
        George Hicks, Selma Jones, Jerry Posner, Stephany Washington
      - Ornette Coleman, undated; 1 open reel audiotapes; 7-inch tape (Box 91)
        (0026819163)
      - Out of Black Newark, January 11, 971; 1 open reel audiotapes; 7-inch reel (Box 92)
        (0026818647, 0026819198)
      - Rap Brown, undated; 1 open reel audiotapes; 5-inch reel (Box 93)
        (0026818671)
      - Recording of the First AfroAmerican Wedding in this Country, May 19, 1967; 1 open reel audiotapes; 7-inch reel (Box 92)
        (0026817926)
      - Rhythm and blues by Leroi Jones, 1974-01-26T00:00:00+00:00; 1 open reel audiotapes; 5-inch tape (Box 92)
        (0026819244)
      - Roi, 11/07/59 and Radio Play, 02/60, 1959-1960; 1 open reel audiotapes; 7-inch reel (Box 92)
        (0026817845)
      - Roy Innis, Queen Mother Moore, Chairman Henry, Betty Shabazz, undated; 1 open reel audiotapes; 12-inch reel (Box 94)
        (0026819384)
      - Rutgers Site, Burning House, undated; 1 open reel audiotapes; 5-inch reel (Box 93)
        (0026818485)
      - Soul Rally, December 7; 1 open reel audiotapes; 7-inch reel (Box 92)
        (0026818019)
      - Souls of Black Folk, January 26, 1975; 6 open reel audiotapes; 7-inch reel (Box 92)
        (0026819031, 0026818620, 0026817969, 0026818884, 0026819082, 0026818000)
      - That old black magic, etc.; I mean you, undated; 1 open reel audiotapes; 5-inch reel (Box 93)
        (0026818698)
      - To Baraka from the Zambian Student Union in the Americas, undated; 1 open reel audiotapes; 5-inch reel (Box 93)
        (0026818582)
      - Traditional Music from Cameroun, 1967; 1 open reel audiotapes; 7-inch reel (Box 92)
        (0026818558)
      - Untitled, undated; 1 open reel audiotapes; 7-inch tape (Box 91)
        (0026817837)
        Act I. Overture: Miles Davis, Sketches of Spain. 1) Bach trio 2) Mary solo 3) Duet Ronny and Judy 4) Godawful Elisa solo 5) Spirituals (everyone)
        Commercial - not digitized
      - Untitled, undated; 1 open reel audiotapes; 7-inch tape (Box 91)
        (0026819210)
        Side 1, Track 1: Baraka Day, Baraka Night, Turner. Track 2: Strickland, Conflicting Ideologies. Side II: Military/Industrial/Union Complex, Conflicting Ideologies (continued), Pan Africanism
      - Untitled, April 6, 1970; 1 open reel audiotapes; 7-inch reel (Box 92)
        (0026818663)
      - Untitled, undated; 1 open reel audiotapes; 5-inch reel (Box 93)
        (0026818469)
        BLANK
      - Untitled B, undated; 1 open reel audiotapes; 5-inch reel (Box 93)
        (0026818035)
      - Untitled C, undated; 1 open reel audiotapes; 7-inch reel (Box 93)
        (0026818450)
      - Untitled D, undated; 1 open reel audiotapes; 7-inch reel (Box 93)
        (0026818612)
      - WBAI Broadcast, January 20, 1980; 3 open reel audiotapes; 7-inch aand two 12-inch reels (Box 93)
        (0026819201, 0026819368, 0026819376)
      - WNY_, 1978; 1 open reel audiotapes; 7-inch reel (Box 92)
        (0026818531)
    - Records, 1973-1980
      - The Dial-A-Poem Poets-Sugar, Alcohol, & Meat, 1980 (Box 86)
      - The Dial-A-Poem Poets-Totally Corrupt, 1976 (Box 86)
      - Wanda Robinson-Me and a Friend, 1973 (Box 86)
      - Edward Dorn-The North Atlantic Turbine, undated (Box 86)
      - The Advanced Workers with the Anti-Imperialist Singers, 1976 (Box 86)
      - The Advanced Workers with the Anti-Imperialist Singers, 1976 (Box 67)
      - The Advanced Workers with the Anti-Imperialist Singers, 1976; 1 phonograph records; 7-inch (Box 82D)
        Side A: So You Was Dancin Need to be Marchin So You Can Dance Some More Later O. Side B: Better Red Let Others Be Dead. JHU-1001
  - Beta and U-Matic, 1972-1976
    - Unlabeled, undated (Box 83)
    - Urban Minority Workshop, 12/14/1976; 1 videocassettes (U-matic) (Box 83)
    - Walter Rodney (Tapes), undated; 1 videotape; Betacam SP tape (Box 83)
      Vidipax Job #3041 Reel #1
    - #67 Women in the Struggle D.C., 1974; 1 videotape; Betacam SP tape (Box 83)
      Vidipax Job #3041 Reel #5
    - Stokely and Chairman, undated; 1 videotape; Betacam SP tape (Box 83)
      Vidipax Job #3041 Reel #2
    - Sonia Sanchez, 05/13/1972; 1 videotape; Betacam SP tape (Box 83)
      Vidipax Job #3041 Reel #4
    - Pan-African Reception (Tape 1), 11/24/1974; 1 videotape; Betacam SP tape (Box 83)
      Vidipax Job #3042 Reel #1
    - untitled, undated; 1 videotape; Betacam SP tape (Box 83)
      possibly blank
  - DVD, 2004-2007
    - Pan African Reception, November 24, 1974; 1 DVDs (Box 82D)
      Tape 10-1201-11 (Beta)
    - Reisinger Auditorium, 2004
      - Coltrane, Monk, and Jazz Criticism, 2004; 1 DVDs (Box 82D)
      - Black Pearls: Blues Women, and What they Say, 2004; 1 DVDs (Box 82D)
      - Blues People, So What, 2004; 1 DVDs (Box 82D)
      - The Rap on the Music Business, 2004; 1 DVDs (Box 82D)
      - African American Dance, 2004; 1 DVDs (Box 82D)
      - Musicians on the Music, Part 1, 2004; 1 DVDs (Box 82D)
      - Musicians on the Music, Part 2, 2004; 1 DVDs (Box 82D)
      - The Poetics of Music, 2004; 1 DVDs (Box 82D)
      - Amiri Baraka and the Blue Ark, 2004; 1 DVDs (Box 82D)
    - The Power of Spoken Word, Volume III: The Legendary Amiri Baraka and the Last Poets, 2005 (Box 86)
    - Our Organization: The Education Program for Those Who Know and Care, 2007 (Box 86)
    - Common Ground Collective-Press Packet, undated (Box 86)
    - Common Ground Collective-Katrina's Child, undated (Box 86)
    - Il cammino delle comete, 2004 (Box 86)
    - Baraka 12: Stokely and Chairman, 1 DVDs (Box 82D)
      Tape 10-1201-19 (1/2'' helical)
    - Hip Hop Won't Stop: Arts and Activism Workshop, 1 DVDs (Box 82D)
  - Film, 1961-1975
    - Afrikan Free School, undated; 1 film reels; 12-inch film reel (Box 85)
    - untitled, undated; 1 film reels; 7-inch film reel (Box 87)
    - untitled, undated; 1 film reels; 7-inch film reel (Box 87)
    - Stirling St. and Howard St., undated; 1 film reels; 7-inch film reel (Box 87)
    - Documentary 2, undated; 2 film reels; Two 5-inch film reels (Box 87)
      PRES085456
    - Cellar Vigil, 1966; 1 film reels; 7-inch film reel (Box 87)
      PRES085448
    - I'm A Man, undated; 1 film reels; 9-inch film reel (Box 84)
    - Kids Working, undated; 1 film reels; 3-inch film reel (Box 84)
    - The Music Business Exposed, 1966; 1 film reels; 3-inch film reel (Box 84)
    - Black Student Union, undated; 1 film reels; 3-inch film reel (Box 84)
    - Reel #3, undated; 1 film reels; 3-inch film reel (Box 84)